A Guide to the Virginia Quartermaster's Department Records, 1861-1864
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Quartermaster's Department records, 1861-1864 (bulk 1861-1863)
Library of Virginia
39376
10.78 cubic feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Acquired prior to 1905 (no other acquisition information available).
Biographical/Historical Information
An ordinance to provide for the organization of Staff Departments for the Military Forces of the State was passed by the Virginia Convention on 21 April 1861 and amended and re-enacted on 24 April 1861. This ordinance organized the Adjutant General's Department, Quartermaster's Department, Subsistence Department, Medical Department, Pay Department, and Engineer Corps. The Quartermaster's Department was to consist of a quartermaster general with the rank of colonel, an assistant quartermaster general with the rank of lieutenant colonel, two quartermasters of the rank of major, and four assistant quartermasters with the rank of captain. On April 21, the Advisory Council ordered that the governor immediately organize the subsistence and quarter-master's departments, placing at the head of each, temporarily, one person with the rank of major, with authority to employ the necessary clerks and assistants. The Board recommended Benjamin Franklin Ficklin for this task.
A second ordinance was passed on 27 April 1861 concerning the Quartermaster's Department, but subsequently repealed on 30 April. This ordinance was replaced by an ordinance "for the better regulation of the Departments of the Army and Navy of Virginia, and for the audit and settlement of Accounts and Claims arising in the present emergency for the defence of the Commonwealth." An ordinance passed by the Convention on 30 April 1861 created a board of commissioners consisting of George W. Munford, J.R. Tucker, and J. M. Bennett, to better regulate the accounts of the Army and Navy and for the audit and settlement of accounts and claims. Edward H. Fitzhugh served as Examining Clerk of the accounts. This Auditing Board continued to pay some officers and settle claims after Governor Letcher issued a proclamation on 6 June 1861 stating that "all Quarter Master, commissary, and medical stores belonging to the State and in charge of said officers be turned over for the use of the Confederate States upon proper receipts for the articles turned over, to be forwarded to the accounting officer for settlement."
The Quartermaster's Dept. remained an important institution during the war as a result of the act passed by the General Assembly on 15 May 1862 creating the Virginia State Line under Maj. Gen. John B. Floyd. The Virginia State Line consisted of approximately 2000 men and was established to recover the western part of the state and protect the salt mines in that region. On 20 May 1862, the Quartermaster's office was moved from Richmond to Lynchburg with a quartermaster depot in Wytheville to assist the supplying of these new forces. The office was later ordered by Governor Letcher to be moved back to Richmond on 7 May 1863. The Virginia State Line forces were short-lived, however, and an act was passed on 28 February 1863 transferring the State Troops and Rangers to the Confederate Government. The Quartermaster's Dept., however, continued to settle the claims of the Virginia State Line, etc., into 1864.
Scope and Content Information
These records relate to expenses incurred by the Quartermaster's Department between 1861 and 1864, but predominantly between 1861 and 1863, for the defense of the Commonwealth. The records are arranged in alphabetical order by the name of the quartermaster officer who submitted these accounts to the Auditing Board for examination and approval. Within each quartermaster, the accounts are arranged in chronological order by year then by quarter. Included are abstracts of expenses, accounts current, correspondence, payrolls, property returns, abstracts of provisions, receipts, vouchers, and other sundry items. Oversized items can be found at the rear of the collection. The abstracts are usually lettered A through N in each quarter and record each voucher by number. The abstracts summarize the information on each voucher including the name of the company or individual selling the items, the date of purchase, the quantity and cost, and a total amount. Most of the quartermaster accounts relate to clothing, transportation, military stores, and camp equipage. In addition, there are payrolls for persons employed in the Quartermaster's Office. These can be found with L.R. Smoot's accounts. Noteworthy items include some of the early vouchers signed by prominent figures during the Civil War including J.E.B. Stuart, Stonewall Jackson, John B. Floyd, Turner Ashby, Joseph E. Johnston, and others.
There is a small amount of correspondence in this collection. Some of the correspondence accompanies the accounts of the quartermaster. This correspondence usually transmits the accounts from the quartermaster officer to Edward H. Fitzhugh, P.F. Howard, or J. Bell Bigger of the Auditing Board. Other correspondence provides a report to the Auditing Board from the quartermasters. In addition, there is a separate file for correspondence arranged in chronological order between 1862 and 1863. Correspondents include L.R. Smoot, Quartermaster General; William H. Richardson, Adjutant General; Edward H. Fitzhugh, Examining Clerk; J.B. Goodloe, Assistant Quartermaster of the Virginia State Line; George W. Munford, Secretary of the Commonwealth; Governor John Letcher; Henry Hill, Paymaster General; and others. This later correspondence is similar to that mentioned above, but also encloses bonds and oaths of office for assistant quartermasters, receipts and invoices, and claims for pay.
Miscellaneous items include a list of quartermaster officers appointed by Acting Quartermaster General, Henry Heth, in 1861. There are also transportation vouchers from the Richmond & Danville Railroad in 1862. Finally, there are miscellaneous accounts that do not appear to belong to a particular quartermaster between 1862 and 1863.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically.
Contents List
- Carruthers, William H.
  - Special Account - Vouchers, Nos. 1-40, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Special Account - Vouchers, Nos. 41-100, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Special Account - Vouchers, Nos. 101-170, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Special Account - Vouchers, Nos. 171-213, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1863 January-June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1863 July-December (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Echols, R.J.
  - Property accounts, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Requisitions of provisions, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Ficklin, B.F.
  - Accounts of expenditures, reports, and related documents, 1861-1863 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers and requests for transportation, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Goodloe, J. B.
  - Abstract A - Vouchers - Book No. 1, Nos. 1-59, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers - Book No. 2, Nos. 60-117, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers - Book No. 3, Nos. 118-173, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers - Book 4, Nos. 174-177 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-100, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 101-159, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-34, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-23, 1862, 3rd Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 1-71, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Abstract L and N - Vouchers, Nos. 1-7, 1862, 3rd Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-24, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-50, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 51-119, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-36, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 37-95, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-40, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Abstract F - Vouchers, Nos. 1-20, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-88, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 1-63, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 3-14, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-32, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Abstract N, 1862, 4th Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-12, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers (Fractional), Nos. 1-30, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-30, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 31-52, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, No. 53, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, No. 54, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, No. 55, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 56-61, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers (Fractional), Nos. 1-42, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-8, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers (Fractional), Nos. 1-6, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Abstract F - Vouchers (Fractional), Nos. 1-14, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers (Fractional), Nos. 1-35, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 1-24, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-2, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers (Fractional), Nos. 1-5, 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-12, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers (Fractional), Nos. 1-16, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Abstract N - Vouchers (and Fractional), 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Property Return, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, No. 35, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, No. 46, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, No. 47, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 48-136, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-21, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-7, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-8, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Abstract N - Vouchers, No. 1, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, No. 1, 1863, 3rd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-27, 1863, 3rd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-7, 1863, 3rd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Abstracts M and N, 1863, 3rd Quarter (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Harman, John A.
  - Property Returns, 1861, 2nd Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 3-7, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Abstract D, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Abstract E, 1861, 2nd Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Abstract F - Vouchers, Nos. 426-480, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-110, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 111-192, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Abstract K-O, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 1-34 - 1st Regiment Artillery, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 35-76 - Kentucky Regiment, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 77-112 - 5th Regiment Infantry, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 114-133 - 4th Regiment Infantry, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 134-155 - 3rd Regiment Infantry, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 156-206 - 2nd Regiment Infantry, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 207-218 - 1st Regiment Infantry, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 219-226 - 6th Regiment Infantry, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 226.5-264 - Maryland Volunteers, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 265-275 - 4th Alabama Regiment, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 276-283 - 2nd and 11th Mississippi Regiment, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 284-292 - Cadets, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 292.5-318, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 319-362 - Naval Battery, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 363-373 - Headquarters, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 374-383 - Hospital, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 384-388 - Transportation Agent (Price, M.E.), 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 389-392 - Superintendent of Rifles (Burkhart, P.), 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 393-398 - Forage Dept., 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 399-401 - Ordnance Dept., 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 402-404 - Commissary Dept., 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 405-411 - Guard House, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 412-425 - Sundry Persons, 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Johnson, J.K.
  - Abstract A, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-100, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 101-200, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 201-299, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers (Subsistence), Nos. 1-42, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-100, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 101-200, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 201-297, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers (Disbursements), Nos. 1-24, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Abstract Bb - Vouchers, Nos. 1-7, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Abstract D, 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-63, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-25, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-35, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Abstract I, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 1-66, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-26, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-77, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-64, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Abstract N, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Lechenet, L.
  - Accounts, 1862, 4th Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Accounts, 1862, 4th Quarter - October (See Oversize) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Accounts, 1862, 4th Quarter - November (See Oversize) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Accounts, 1862, 4th Quarter - December (See Oversize) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Abstract of Provisions Issued - Vouchers, Nos. 2-15, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 7-12, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Abstract F, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-3, 1862, 4th Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Abstract I - Vouchers, Nos. 1-8, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 7-78, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-2, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-5, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Accounts, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Accounts, 1863, 1st Quarter - January (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Accounts, 1863, 1st Quarter - February (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Accounts, 1863, 1st Quarter - March (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-67, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Abstract A - Sub-vouchers, Nos. 1-7 and 1-10, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-24, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers - Commissary Expenditures, Nos. 1-32, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Abstract D, 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Abstract E, 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-3, 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Abstract L, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-10, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Accounts
  - Misc. accounts, 1862 January-June (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Misc. accounts, 1862 July-August (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Misc. accounts, 1862 September-October (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Misc. accounts, 1862 November-December (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Misc. accounts, 1863 January (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Misc. accounts, 1863 February-July (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Officers Appointed
  - Officers appointed, 1861 (See Oversize) (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Richmond and Danville Railroad Co.
  - Vouchers, Nos. 1-50, 1862 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 51-80, 1862 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers, Nos. 81-105, 1862 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Rocke, Floyd G.
  - Abstracts and vouchers, 1862, 4th Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-2, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-8, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 1-10, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Abstract L, 1862, 4th Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Abstract N, 1862, 4th Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Abstract of Purchases - Vouchers, Nos. 1-3, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Commissary Returns, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-36, 1863, 1st Quarter - January (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 37-62, 1863, 1st Quarter - February (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 63-128, 1863, 1st Quarter - March (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Abstract B, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Abstract C - Vouchers, Nos. 1-3, 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Abstract D - Vouchers, Nos. 1-12, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-6, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Abstract F, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-24, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Abstract I, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 1-14, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-3, 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Abstract M, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Abstract of Purchases - Vouchers, Nos. 1-13, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Commissary Returns, 1863, 1st Quarter - January (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Commissary Returns, 1863, 1st Quarter - February (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Commissary Returns, 1863, 1st Quarter - March (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Abstract M, 1863, 2nd Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Commissary Returns, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Property account and Statement of differences for 4th Quarter 1862 and 1st Quarter 1863, 1864 (See Oversize) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1862-1863 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Smoot, L. R.
  - Abstract A, 1861, 3rd Quarter (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-60, 1861, 3rd Quarter (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, No. 61-79, 1861, 3rd Quarter (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Abstract D, 1861, 3rd Quarter (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Abstract M, 1861, 3rd Quarter (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-52, 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 53 (Abstract 1 - Vouchers 1-28), 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 53 (Abstract 2 - Vouchers 1-50), 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 53 (Abstract 2 - Vouchers 51-100), 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 53 (Abstract 2 - Vouchers 101-144), 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 54-97, 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 98-150, 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 151-183, 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Abstract A, 1862, 1st Quarter (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-20, 1862, 1st Quarter (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-70, 1862, 1st Quarter (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 71-104, 1862, 1st Quarter (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Abstract D and E, 1862, 1st Quarter (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-6, 1862, 1st Quarter (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-12, 1862, 1st Quarter (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Abstract A, 1862, 2nd Quarter (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-12, 1862, 2nd Quarter (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-43, 1862, 2nd Quarter (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Abstract E and L, 1862, 2nd Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-5, 1862, 2nd Quarter (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Abstract A, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-69, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, No. 1, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-14, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Abstract B - Contingent expenditures - Vouchers, Nos. 2-39 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Abstract C - Vouchers, Nos. 1-3, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Abstract A - Advances to Officers "Floyd's Army" - Vouchers, Nos. 1-10, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Abstract E and L, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-37, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Abstract N, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous accounts (unnumbered vouchers), 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Abstract A, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-75, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 76-105, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, No. 106, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-20, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-30, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 31-50, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 51-80, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 81-82, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 83-84, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 85-109, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Abstract C - Vouchers, Nos. 1-18, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Abstract D - Vouchers, Nos. 1-2, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-11, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, No. 1, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-4, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, No. 1, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-51, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 11)